Oh my god, Yuche!
We have- AHHHHHH!
Told you I'll be here forever!
Oh my god...
A la Cat's Eye!
Hey Vogue, it's Cat's Eye!
And today we're making virgin piña coladas, carbo bulldog, and chocolate cupcakes.
Let's get started!
Megan is sick, so she couldn't- Megan doesn't feel well today!
Yeah, she doesn't feel well, so she couldn't be here, but she is here in spirit.
We're gonna start off with virgin piña coladas.
We have some pineapple juice, coconut cream, some ice, and then to garnish we have some pineapple and cherries and then some cute little umbrellas too
to just put on top.
Do you want to start us off by pouring?
Can we give her a tiny mix?
I feel like it's like gone to the bottom.
Yeah, let's give it a little mix.
Should we be like, yes.
Yes.
Yeah.
So don't pour all of it.
We're just gonna pour enough and then leave a little bit behind.
Go for it.
I'm going to let you do this.
Okay.
Let's get some towels.
I'm sorry.
I've never mastered the art of pouring things because it always comes out from the bottom.
Beautiful.
Tiny bit more.
Perfect.
Add all of this coconut cream.
Coconut water.
Okay.
Oh.
Yes.
It kind of looks like mochi.
It's creamy.
It's so creamy.
I don't think anyone's the worst cook.
Well, you don't cook.
There's no worst cook.
No, no.
Oh.
No, there's no worst cook here.
It's just...
I just don't cook.
I don't try to do it.
I just order food all the time.
I've only ever seen her make eggs.
Yeah, my eggs are fire.
Want soup?
Yeah, not one scoop.
Just get it up until the top.
Yeah, fill the whole cup.
One or two cups.
Can you tell it's our first time?
Trust me, you have to fill the whole cup.
Yeah, it's the full cup.
And then we're going to put it here in the blender.
Of the full cup.
Yeah.
Pour it in.
Don't.
A cup is like this.
I'm scared.
That's five.
I'm scared it's going to splash.
It's okay.
It won't splash.
A virgin King of Colada is so nostalgic.
Okay, now we're going to...
You know, I've never actually had one.
No, really?
Okay, this is my favorite drink because it's like...
It's like vacation.
Wait, can we put a little more pineapple juice?
More pineapple juice?
Yeah, just a little.
Why not?
It's looking a bit too creamy.
No, it's not supposed to look too yellow.
Why not?
I like creamy.
Okay, it's fine.
Why not?
Okay, okay.
You weren't supposed to put it all, but okay.
Sure.
You have to just go by the...
What?
Yay!
What was that?
Where did that come from?
That almost...
Wait, okay, more ice.
Okay, I think that's enough.
That's great, Inche.
We're gonna mime our deepest, darkest secret.
You guys will never know.
Oh!
What?
She just scared me for no reason.
Okay, ready?
Deepest, darkest secret.
She's never gonna know.
Oh!
One thing I truly cannot do is read lips.
She's the worst.
I really wish I could.
It frustrates me so much because there's so many times we have to speak to each other that way and I can't do it.
She's actually the worst.
This is delicious.
Wait, is it ready?
Oh, it's ready?
That's so easy.
That looks magnificent.
Do you guys all want to have matching umbrellas?
Pink for Pinky Up.
I'm going to do blue.
Oh, okay.
She wants to be different.
Pinky up.
Pinkies up and Tanya Kolata.
We have these little pineapple garnish and like a little cherry because we love.
Thanks.
Because Megan is here in spirit.
Cheers.
You have to look me in the eye.
Oh no!
Let's go.
Your umbrella.
Oh, umbrella.
Told you I'll be here forever.
I love opening this.
Said I'll always be friends.
I'm gonna stick it out till the end.
Cheers!
Mmm, that's beautiful.
That's delicious.
Come on.
Come on!
Now we're gonna make Buldak.
It's carbo Buldak.
There's onion and there's garlic mozzarella cheese.
Chili oil?
Chili garlic oil.
Scallions and horikake.
Sesame oil, which is my favorite.
Sesame oil.
And soy sauce and chicken and cream.
Heavy cream?
Vegetable oil.
And eggs.
And don't forget the buldak!
And The Buldak!
And Buldak!
I really want to fry the eggs because that's really the only thing I know how to make.
Wait, should we switch?
You can fry it here.
I can go here so I can help with this.
Are we making two?
Let's make all of them!
There's four of them!
Oh wait, you're right.
But anyways, we have our single "Animal" and it just came out.
It's really fun.
I don't think we've ever made a song like "Animal" before.
You should transform into Ed Sheeran.
She literally sounds like that.
He definitely wrote the song, and you can hear his influence for sure.
I was in the recording studio when you recorded it.
Wait, should I try it?
Okay, you want to listen to mine?
Yeah.
Five, six, seven, eight.
I can't go that low.
She just turned into Ed Sheeran.
Spirit of Eb.
Well, our new EP that's about to come out is called *Wild*.
It's wild.
It feels like our last EP, *Beautiful Chaos*, is older sister.
The same kind of world, but I think visually it's all a bit weirder.
Does that make sense?
Like, it's all a bit more developed and mature, and I think a bit more interesting.
If I would say, like, than the last one, it just feels like we've grown.
We have a better understanding of, like, who we are as one.
You can hear that in the album.
I will start on that.
We want to make it a little soupy, right?
We know how to eat ramen.
We all made Buldak like two days ago.
Yoonchae put it in our group chat.
She was like, "I made it last."
I think like sometimes after we rehearse for really long.
Oh my god, Yoonchae.
We rehearse for a long time, and we rehearse very late at night.
So sometimes Buldak feels like the only option.
Six, seven hours.
We used to do like 12-hour days.
Now it's like six hours.
We used to have like, we wake up at 8, we go to rehearsal, we finish at this time.
More routine.
Now it's like, different thing every day.
But I prefer the different thing every day.
Cooking is a really good way.
Really?
It feels like rewarding, eating something that you made with your hands.
You guys know I'm stressed when I bake for you guys.
She just baked blondies.
Yeah, that's something that my therapist told me to do because he knows that I love cooking and I love baking.
And so he told me if I want to practice my perfectionism, like being such a perfectionist and wanting to do everything correct, I just need to bake
because it's such a science.
So I just follow the recipe exactly, try to do that perfectly.
And then it's like, that's where I practice my release, me wanting to be perfect and always put together and all that stuff.
Here where we might differ, I like it really spicy.
I do too.
Can we add all of it?
I would like to add all of it.
Let go.
I'm so glad that we all like spicy food.
Yeah.
Like these two.
I gonna look like a cat under the rain.
Like I gonna start sweating.
It's gonna start sweating on my nose.
I used to cook gul-dal or ramen like every single day.
The eggs are almost done.
I like to put the chili oil as I'm cooking it.
Can we do that?
And also the sesame oil.
Oh my god, that smells insane.
That smells amazing.
I'm so hungry too.
I think we'll put the cheese in, and then we'll put the chicken on top.
With eggs.
I love the smell of sesame oil, you guys.
Wait, what?
Wait, you put soy sauce in?
It's so good.
Yes, it's so good.
You're just like...
It's so good.
Did I just commit a crime?
Because I'm the person who, like, cooks original.
Like, just...
Wait, did I just do something bad?
No, no, no.
No, you're not.
No, you don't do anything, but...
It's just like, I'm just shocked.
Oh, I'm listening to a lot of SZA right now.
I love her.
And then a lot of Daft Punk.
Obviously, Erykah Badu.
I love R&B.
I listen to a lot of rap.
Don Toliver, Drake's new three albums.
I love that.
Yeah, like a lot.
I love it cheesy.
But also mozzarella cheese makes the Buldak saltier.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So let's start.
And there's no need for putting salt on the eggs right now.
Just a little bit.
Like little.
Because the eggs need salt.
They need salt.
Okay, the eggs are done.
Guys, look at.
The eggs.
I could never make an egg.
I have tricks that I learned from me, myself, and I, and Gordon Ramsey.
Taste test?
Look at how cheesy it looks.
Guys, a chef always needs to taste test.
Yay.
Wait guys, I'm sorry.
Oh my god.
Is it giving?
Mmm.
It's fire, isn't it?
No.
Guys, I'm swallowing.
It's fire.
Oh my god, it's really spicy.
But is it good?
Yes, it's giving.
Mama!
Yay!
Serve me mama!
My turn!
Y'all are like little birdies when they're ready for their mom to like give them the worms in their mouth.
Can I go for it?
Yeah, go topping them.
Wait, I want some of that sauce.
Okay, let's have more.
We're like forgetting so many things right now.
We have so many.
We're too excited.
Whoa, that looks so good.
Guys, I don't think I can wait.
I need to eat this right now.
You guys, look at this.
Can we get a close-up of this?
Can I go towards the camera right now?
Come back here, guys.
Stay in line.
This is how intimate this needs to be, guys.
Oh my god.
I love that side.
Are you guys ready to eat?
Okay, okay.
Yes.
Oh, we're eating already?
What?
No cheers, just get straight into it.
That's fire.
Woo!
I felt a physical like heat flash right...
and I just started sweating.
Wow.
Really?
And it's just one bite.
Okay, now we're gonna decorate some lovely chocolate cupcakes that our wonderful culinary producer Jeannie made for us.
Thank you Jeannie!
Woo!
Okay, so we have all these decorations.
I think to each their own right?
To each their own.
I'll take the smallest one.
I kind of want the biggest one.
Or do you want the biggest one?
I take a medium.
I wanted to get the biggest on the top because it just more space to decorate.
Me, Sophia, and Danny.
I'm sorry, you guys, I just love frosting.
I just have to.
Wait, I need to taste the frosting.
What kind of frosting is it?
I need to taste the frosting first, Sophia.
Is it my favorite or your favorite?
Is it ours?
Wait, me too, me too.
Wait, I'm trying this.
It's amazing.
I think my favorite thing we've done so far is Coachella or Lollapalooza.
I think the festivals always have the best, best, best energy.
Also, our Grammy nomination, our VMA win, AMA win.
VMA win.
Huge milestone things have happened back to back to back in this last year.
Five years ago, would you have ever imagined yourself?
No.
What the heck?
Not at all.
Not this soon.
We always talk about how we saw Coachella and Grammys and stuff like that as like 10 years down the line.
And it happened two years down the line.
So we have a lot of gratitude.
This one is like, I love Disney, so I'm going to make it almost like Disney-ers.
We love our icons.
They are like the most passionate fans I've ever seen.
Like I think they are just so, they've been with us a lot of the icons.
We did the same thing.
Sorry.
Oh, yeah, we always do.
We always do the same thing.
We always have the same taste and aesthetic.
The icons, like a lot of the icons, were there with us since we were training and since we were in Dream Academy, which is our competition
show, and they were the ones that voted us to be in the group.
So the fans played a very big part and why we were here today.
I mean, they played the entire.
It's truly no cat's eye without our icons.
Yes.
Genuinely, genuinely do love our icons so much, and we always want that to be felt through our performances, and we wanted you guys to feel that we're
truly grateful.
We wouldn't have all these awards, these nominations, these spots in these festivals, or anything really, if it isn't for them consuming our art and everything and
supporting us and telling their friends about us.
Wait, okay, I'm gonna make Megan one.
I'm gonna put this pink.
Look at how cute this is.
Two cherries for Megan.
We have pop rocks.
Are you serious?
Pop rocks?
Yes.
Stop.
Oh, I don't really like them.
Guys, we have.
We're gonna make a wild cupcake.
I made a lot of wild cupcakes.
Should we make a cupcake and put every single topping on it?
Isn't it cute?
Okay, you got creative there.
She's such a little.
Artist.
Wait, it's like they're swimming.
Yes.
They're swimming.
I'm going to add one of everything.
Ready?
Here.
Here's some of that.
No, you ruined my ears.
Va va voom.
Wait, I have to add this to my practice kit.
Some of the wet and messy, and some of the purple.
Sophia's an ally.
Yes.
I want some more frosting.
It's going to get on your jacket.
Wait, I think that's everything, right?
Is it?
Yeah, I want more.
Why is no one putting this in?
I don't want to.
Because it's big.
Yeah, put it, do it.
Wait, but I love these.
I'm going to hold my OG.
Yeah, same.
I'm going to hold up the spoon of frosting.
It's so dirty.
But it has fur on it.
Want it?
Thanks for having us, Vogue!
Stream our new EP, Wild, that comes out August 14th, and go stream Animal and Pinky up.
Cheers!
Bye!